Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy, Dean's Office; Records ua680
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The GSPA records contains annual reports, dean's office correspondence, budget documents, evaluation reports, plans, publications, student research essays, training program manuals, workshop materials, meeting minutes, course descriptions and reading lists. The majority of records originate from the Dean's office subject files. The two major exceptions are the records originating from Hannah Applebaum, the school's librarian from approximately 1963-1971, and the Organization & Methods program (1946-60) records of Murray Nathan, the Director of the Office of Planning and Procedures in the New York State Department of Health. The original file names, where available, were kept when possible and the records are primarily arranged by subject series.
The records relate to the founding of the school and its integration into the SUNY system in 1962 and then into University at Albany in 1966. The records also document the school's development and administrative history and its programs in political science, public administration, public affairs and political economy. There are also dean's office records concerning the development and programs of the school's centers and institutes. The most prominent centers, the Comparative Development Studies Center, the Center for Women in Government, and the Institute for Government and Policy Studies, are more thoroughly documented through their respective records contained in the University Archives.
The GSPA records cover the period from 1946-1989. The bulk of the material covers the time period from 1962-1983. It is possible that additional records and materials relating to the early history and administration of the school (prior to 1962) may be located at Syracuse University and New York University due to the school's original structure as a joint program of the two universities. There are no annual reports of the dean prior to 1962 or after 1979, although there are a number of other annual reports available for 1980. The records include many evaluation reports regarding the school and its programs. Some of the individual reports are gathered into Series 1, Subseries 6, but the remainder are widely scattered throughout the records. There are no department-specific subject files prior to 1968, but the school did not begin to adopt a departmental organizational structure until after its integration into the University at Albany in 1966. There is detailed information regarding GSPA courses and reading lists contained in the Hannah Applebaum series for 1963-71. There is some additional information relating to courses and reading lists available but these are scattered throughout the records. The additional files are generally less complete, particularly after about 1974. There are relatively few examples of publications issued by GSPA's related centers and institutes, with the exception of the Local Government Studies Center. There is a large collection of Local Government Studies Center publications and it includes a complete run of Metropolitan Area Problems and Metropolitan Area Digest together with the cumulative index (1957-1971). The student research essays available in the records are disproportionately representative of the 1960s, although there is some material from the early 1970s included in the records. Faculty publications cover the 1960s and the 1970s, and the records include a few items from the early 1980s. Reprints of faculty written journal articles are only available for the 1960s. Workshop and training program materials in the records generally only represent either the Public Executive Project or the Public Service Training Program, and contain materials from ca. 1975- 86. There are a few additional materials relating to workshops conducted during the 1970s contained in the faculty publications Subseries. The records do not contain any organized or complete collection of publications such school view books, program pamphlets, brochures or commencement programs. There are scattered examples of these types of items in the records, but these disproportionately represent the 1980s. Most examples of publications of this type are contained within the GSPA and Rockefeller College records Subseries.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into 10 file series based on their original use.
Acquisition Information
These records were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives, University Libraries, University at Albany, the Graduate School of Public Affairs in several separate records transfers ca. 1983-1992
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted, with the exception of the student papers in Series 10 which are restricted.
Political Science; Public policy and administration; Higher education and state.; Higher Education Administration; Web Archives; UAlbany Schools & Colleges; State University of New York at Albany; State University of New York at Albany. Graduate School of Public Affairs
- Reports, Plans, and Budgets, 1962-1985; 1; 2.5 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of annual report of the dean (1962-64, 1967-79), department annual reports (1978-79, 1979-80) and center, institute and program reports (1979-80).
  This series consists Dean's files, 1971-1984, including correspondence (1971-84), memoranda (1971-2, 1977-83), budgets (1975), supply and expenses budgets (1979-8 1), preliminary budget requests (1973 - 74), final budget proposals and requests (1973-74, 1977-78, 1979-80, 1982-84), tentative temporary service allocation plans (1972-3), faculty line projections (1971-3), descriptive statements(1981-83), and plans and 5 year plans(1982-84).
  This series contains correspondence, meeting agendas and memoranda relating to: the Dean's Council and smaller committees; task force reports and other evaluations of GSPA; GSPA plans and planning documents; programs and priorities, 1961-1967, 1969-1971, 1974-1981; structure and re-organization, 1962-1964, 1969-1971, 1973-1975. Three is also information regarding the school's integration into SUNY and later into the University at Albany (1962-64, 1969-71).
  - Academic Policy (Includes Report of Educational Policies Committee 1969), 1969-1971 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 1)
  - Academic Policy Committee-Reorganization of GSPA Meeting, 1973 February 12 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 2)
  - Academic Policy Committee, 1974-1979 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 3)
  - Academic Program Priorities, 1975; 1980 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 4)
  - Academic Programs and Priorities, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 5)
  - Academic Plan of GSPA, Reorganization of GSPA, 1965-1975 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 6)
  - Academic Programs and Priorities, 1975-1980 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 7)
  - Academic Programs and Priorities, 1980-1982 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 8)
  - Annual Reports, 1962-1963, July 15 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1963-1964, October 10 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 10)
  - Annual Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 12)
  - Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 13)
  - Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 16)
  - Annual Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 17)
  - Annual Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 19)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 21)
  - Annual Reports, Dean's, Departments, Public Executive Project, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 22)
  - Annual Reports, No Dean's Report, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 23)
  - Budget Correspondence, Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 24)
  - Preliminary Budget Request and Five Year Projections, June 5, 1972, Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 25)
  - Final Budget Request, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 27)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 28)
  - Dean's Council, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 29)
  - Dean's Council, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 30)
  - Assistance to the Dean, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 31)
  - Educom, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 32)
  - NYS Education Department Inspection, 1964 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 33)
  - Finance and Business, 1979-1983 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 34)
  - ASPA Evaluation, 1965 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 35)
  - GSPA Evaluation Report, Excerpts and Summary, 1973 November (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 36)
  - Administrative Self Study and Evaluation, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 37)
  - Objectives, Organization and Programs (Budget Request 1966-1967), 1961-1967 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 1)
  - Plans for GSPA, 1963-1965 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 2)
  - GSPA Development Plans, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 3)
  - Three Year Plans, Preliminary Budget Request, 1976-1980 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 4)
  - Revisions of Three Year Plans, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 5)
  - Three Year Plan, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 6)
  - Five Year Plan Updates, 1981-1987 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 7)
  - Five Year Plan Updates, 1983-1988 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 8)
  - Five Year Plans and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 9)
  - GSPA Reports to Trustees, 1963 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 10)
  - Proposal Drafts, Reorganization of GSPA, 1973-1975 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 11)
  - Reorganization of GSPA, Proposal Drafts, 1973 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 12)
  - Reorganization Meeting, Reorganization of GSPA, 1973 June (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 13)
  - Management Reorganization of GSPA, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 14)
  - Structure of GSPA, 1962-1964, 1969-1971 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 15)
  - Five Year Plan Updates, 1983-1990 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 16)
  - SUNYA Task Force on Public Affairs and Policy Education, Research Service, Report to President, 1981 March 31 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 17)
  - Task Force, 1973 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 18)
  - Task Force on Public Affairs and Policy Education, Research, and Service, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 19)
  - UUP, 1974 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 20)
  - Urban Studies, 1979-1981 (Box 2 (1-Reports, Plans, and Budgets), Folder 21)
- Subject and Correspondence Files, 1946-1989; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  This series contains student rosters (1965/66-1970), commencement programs (1963- 64, 1966), profiles, headcounts (1980), lists of student public policy dissertation projects (ca. 1981) and planning documents (1971-3, 1984). The records also include information regarding enrollment in relation to faculty workload and faculty projections (1971-1973)and correspondence (1975-1980) and analysis reports (1977-1980). The records include information on recruitment of minority students and faculty, and the make-up of the workforce and student populations. This series also contains records about: community outreach, 1975, 1980-1981; faculty issues; fellowships, assistantships, and internships, 1971-1983
  - Advisory Committee on Promotions and Tenure, 1972-1974 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - SUNY Albany Semester Program, 1978-1981 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Assistantships and Fellowships, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - Assistantships and Fellowships, 1978-1980 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
  - Civil Service Fellowships, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - Affirmative Action, 1977; 1979-1980 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - SUNY Benevolent Fellowship Program, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - Collective Bargaining Study, 1979 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs, Student Rosters, Institute of Public Administrative Department, 1956-1970 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - Committee on Committees, 1979-1983 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - Community University Day, 1975 September 27 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - Public Service and Community Outreach, 1980-1981 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Judge Rivers, Meeting, 1972 October 12 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - Department of Health, Education, Welfare (HEW), 1976-1978 (Box 2 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - Department of Health, Education, Welfare (HEW), Department Public Service Fellowship, 1976-1978 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Enrollment and Faculty Projections, 1971 September (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Activity Report, Forms, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Activity Report, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Faculty Activity Report, Public Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Faculty Activity Report, Political Science, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Appointment and Allocation, 1967-1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - Faculty Exchange, 1973-1977 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meeting Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Faculty Salaries, Principles and Policy, 1965-1970 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Status Committee, 1966-1969 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Travel, 1966-1968 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - Faculty Workload, 1964; 1970 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - Faculty Workload, 1974-1977 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - Fund for the Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
  - GSPA Faculty Research, 1964-1966 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - GSPA Six Year Bibliography of Faculty, 1968-1973 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
  - GSPA Six Year Bibliography of Faculty, 1968-1973 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - Fall Admissions and Enrollment, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Fall Admissions and Enrollment, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - GSPA, 1962-1970 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
  - GSPA, 1964-1966; 1968-1970 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - GSPA, By-Laws, February and December, 1965 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - GSPA, 1966; 1970 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - GSPA, 1969-1973 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - GSPA, 1970-1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - GSPA, 1971-1974 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - GSPA, 1971; 1975 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - GSPA, 1971-1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - GSPA, 1975-1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - GSPA, ca. 1970-1979; Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - GSPA, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
  - GSPA, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
  - Origins of GSPA, 1950-1955; 1958-1960 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
  - Origins of GSPA, 1956-1961 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
  - History of GSPA, 1960-1968; 1972-1975; 1977 (Box 3 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
  - GSPA Contact Offices, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Course Reading Lists, 1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Job Placement Service, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - GSPA Move to Library Basement, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - GSPA Profiles and Headcounts, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Consideration to Remove GSPA, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Renaming GSPA, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - Grants, 1973-1975; 1977 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - The Helderberg Review, 1971-1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Herbert Humphrey Institute, University of Minnesota, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Fellowships, 1977-1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) Fellowships, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - ICP Cases, Publications, Syracuse Publication List, Undated (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Dr. Bernard Johnpoll, Correspondence from Israel Independent Study Students, 1971 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - Minority Recruitment, 1975; 1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - National Association of Counties, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1976-1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - GSPA Move to Milne Building, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - NASPAA Committee on Comparative and Development Administration, 1972-1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
  - NASPAA Comparative Committee Meeting, San Diego, CA, 1973 March 31 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - NASPAA Comprehensive Schools Section, Meeting, Chicago, IL, (Cancelled by Dean), 1973 October 26 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
  - NASPAA and ASPA Conferences, 1974 May 2-8 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
  - National Public Service Awards, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
  - Nature Conservancy Assistantships, Internship Program, 1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
  - Nature Conservancy Assistantships, Proposed Budgets, 1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
  - Off-Campus Graduate Study (SUNY), 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - Presidential Management Intern Program, 1977-1979 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - Presidential Management Intern Program, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - Presidential Management Intern Program, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - Presidential Management Intern Program, 1980-1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - Programs and Courses, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - Programs and Course Outlines, ca. 1968-1969 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - Public Employee Labor Relations Officials, Correspondence, 1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - Rockefeller College, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - Rockefeller College, 1984 January-July (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - Rockefeller College, 1984 August-1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller College, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
  - Rockefeller College: Annual Distinguished Alumni Awards Banquet, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
  - Rockefeller College, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller College Intern Program, 1986 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller College, 1987 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller College, 1988-1989 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller College Commencement, 1989 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - School of Criminal Justice, Dean's Reports, Memoranda, News Reports, 1972-1983 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - School of Information and Library Science, Memoranda and News Letters, 1977-1979 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - School of Information and Library Science, 1981-1985 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - School of Social Welfare, 1977; 1979-1980; 1983 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Governor's Task Force on the Financing of Higher Education in NYS, 1972-1973 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Proposal for Creation of Albert Schweitzer Professorship, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Schweitzer Chair, 1978-1979 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - University Senate, 1979 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - University Senate, 1980-1983 (Box 5 (2-Subject and Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
- Dean's Day Files, 1967-1982; 3; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series consists of a day file on public administration and policy. Many of the records deal with the New York State Department of Education (NYSED) Political Science Department Report (1978). The records also include information regarding recruitment, faculty, courses, a proposal for a symposium in public policy, and the political science department.